Thank you for the people in this room. The way they work hard, with a given guill and sometimes it's not appreciated please let them know that we care help
rest of our employees and we would thank you for all them do,
for our community. Pray that you will bless the mement tonight with energy and in this room, blessed them
with wisdom. Thank you for the privilege of being from Miami, but also to be a privilege
from the time frame of immediately after-the town hall meeting for following month. Most
of the year. So again, he's definitely is his neck out there to kind
of. Again, with the tipping fees being way that he's going to salvage a lot
of the city. So I had another citizen ask this question,
I guess what i'm asking is, you're talking about one race that these rates on trash
and the biggest bang for your buck.
Because it's kill them. The cost on the trash is whatever just you know,
there's no. There could be a singing deal and kill their, that is totally different
than that. What about Bernan and again, has
the money? So we know it's coming, just a matter of when.
And you said there was a guy coming from Joplin every day.
I think we need to have the discussion
of the day. Would that give you an option?
I know there has been discussion. Mo is told me about some discussions, but i don't